Varshney Aditya

New Delhi, Delhi, India



varshneyaditya28@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/varshneyaditya28

Summary

Tech-savvy React dev based in Delhi, India. Currently enrolled in The third year of Computer Science and Engineering with a Specialization in Data Science. Passionate about CS, Data Science and Deep Learning -Contributed to various open source platforms.

Experience



Open Source Contributor

GirlScript Winter of Contributing Sep 2021 - Nov 2021 (3 months)



Ninja Entrepreneur

Coding Ninjas Apr 2021 - Sep 2021 (6 months)

Education



() AJAY KUMAR GARG ENGINEERING COLLEGE, GHAZIABAD

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science 2020 - 2024



The Air Force School (TAFS), Subroto Park

Pre-university, Science 2018 - 2020



The Air Force School (TAFS), Subroto Park

High School 2007 - 2018

Skills

React.js • Flutter • Data Analysis • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • C++ • Python (Programming Language) • Data Structures • Algorithms